phoneusbdrivers.com 2017-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Phone USB Drivers

## What Information Do We Collect?

At PhoneUSBDrivers.com, we gather user information from our users when you register on the website, subscribe to the newsletter, participate in a survey of fill any type of form. You may be asked for your name, email address, phone number or mailing address.

You may however choose to visit our website anonymously. We will gather non-individual personal information about the users when they interact with our website. This non-personal identification information may include the type of the computer, the name of the web browser, and connection information such as Internet Service provider Information and Operating System.

## What Do We Use Information For?

  * We use all the user collected information to personalize the user experience, the user collected information helps us to respond better to your personal needs.
  * We strive to improve the website based on the user feedback and information collected from the users.
  * We strive to improve the customer service and respond efficiently to the queries and service requests and support needs.
  * We send out periodic emails to users to notify the users of new services and products offered by the website update the users regarding their queries and related information.

## Protecting Your Information

We adopt a large number of security measures to protect your information from unauthorized access, alteration and any type of disclosure. We use appropriate information collection, storing and processing techniques. We adopt appropriate security measures to protect this information against any unauthorized access, disclosure or alteration of this user collected data such as usernames, passwords and transaction information.

Your personal or non-personal information is never exchanged with anyone or sold or rented or transferred to any individual or company without your consent.

## Cookies Usage

If you allow the cookies are saved on user’s hard drive and allow the advertisers and service providers to recognize your computer and process data. Cookies are used to understand the user usage patterns so that we can offer better experience to the users and make their browsing experience more pleasurable. The cookies also allow our advertising partners to track your interests and offer advertisements and ads in which you might be interested.

If users want they can disallow cookies and refuse any kind of tracking. It is worth noting that this kind of behavior may cause issues on the website leading to some functions not working properly.

We use Google Ads in our website for monetization and these uses cookies to serve ads. Google uses DoubleClick DART cookies for this process and you can opt out of it by following this URL: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

## Your Acceptance Of Our Policy

By visiting or using our website it is signified that you agree with our privacy policy and the activities we undertake. If our privacy policy is not in compliance with you then you are requested to not to use the website. Your continued usage is deemed as acceptance of our privacy policy. By using our website you provide your consent to our website privacy policy.

## Changes in Privacy Policy

From time to time we update our privacy policy regarding our website and services and products offered by us. Users are advised to frequently visit the privacy policy to view the new privacy terms. It is requested for the users to keep them updated with the latest changes in the privacy policies.

## Contact Us

If you have any query regarding the privacy policy or the services and products offered by the website you can contact us at: info@phoneusbdrivers.com!
